本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
咱们这片土地上有很多大地洞
In this land of ours, there are many great pits,
但是没有哪口比无底洞更深不见底
but none more bottomless than the bottomless pit,
也就是你们现在看到的这口  它是深不见底的
Which as you can see here, is bottomless.
我有个问题  它是无底的么
Question. Is it bottomless?
孩子们  你们谁能和苏斯解释一下呢
Kids, could one of you try explaining this to Soos?
斯坦叔公  再问一遍  我们干嘛要来这里呢
Grunkle Stan, why are we here again?
为了丢掉我们不喜欢的东西
To dispose of things that we don't want.
再见了  神秘小屋的意见卡
So long, mystery shack suggestion cards.
再见  小吉迪恩写给我的诡异的情书
Goodbye, creepy love letters from Lil' Gideon.
去死吧  去死吧
Die! Die!
你干嘛呢
What are you doing?
扔东西啊  大家不都在扔么
Throwing stuff, dude. Everyone's doing it!
你推的那是啥  梅宝
What you got there, Mabel?
不过是藏着我个人神秘隐私的箱子而已
It's just my personal box of mysterious secrets.
没什么值得好奇的
Nothing worth wondering about!
永别了
Goodbye forever!
斯坦叔公  你非得让我说出严格地讲
Grunkle Stan, do I really have to be the one to point out
任何一个地洞都不可能是无底的么
that a bottomless pit is, by definition, impossible?
你就胡扯吧
Says you!
我觉得我们永远都不会知道了
Well, I guess we'll never know.
啊  感觉像有一股无形的力量在推我们
Aah! It's some sort of invisible pushing force!
快  大家快回小屋
Quick! Everyone back to the shack!
我还没扔完呢
I'm not done getting rid of these yet!
斯坦叔公  别扔了
Grunkle Stan! No!
快扔完了  快了
Almost... almost... almost...
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
CC录制： ufohaman  Qin Cong
时间轴： sunshine
■
翻译： Tracy  怖鲑鲑
校订： Enpistu  WaitinZ
■
后期： Enpistu  WaitinZ
怪诞小镇  第一季第十四集
Gravity Falls  S01E14  Bottomless Pit
我说  还有人想多喊一会儿么
So, anyone wanna scream some more?
我们在哪儿
Where are we?
我们在一个看上去哪儿也不是的地方
We're somewhere where it looks like we're nowhere.
我们最终还是会着陆的
We're gonna land on something eventually.
任何一秒都有可能
Could be any second now!
看来我们得在这儿待上一段时间了
Well, it looks like we're down here for the long haul.
谁想看我用扑克变个魔术
Who wants to see some card tricks?
没啦
Ta-da!
要不咱们来讲故事打发时间吧
Hey! Maybe we should pass the time by tellin' stories.
我有个故事  名字叫  都怪斯坦叔公
I've got a story! It's called: "The time Grunkle Stan
我们全都掉进了无底洞
got us all thrown into a bottomless pit.
而且得在这儿度过余生
Where we spent the rest of our natural lives!"
接着说
Go on.
别这样  迪普  你明明有更好的故事
Come on, Dipper, you can do better than that.
好吧  我给你们讲个故事
Fine. I'll tell you a story,
我管这个故事叫
A story I'd like to call:
声音终结者
Voice over.
准备好了么
Ready?
小猪转圈
Spin the pig! Whoo!
斯坦叔公  你以前亲过猪吗
Hey, Grunkle Stan, ever kissed a pig before?
我才不回答你这个问题
I'm not gonna answer that question.
伙计们  我刚才好像被条蛇咬了
Guys! Guys! I think I just got bit by a snake!
你们快送我去医院
I need you to get me to a hospital quick!
咋了  有什么好笑的
What? What's so funny?
抱歉  就是你用你那可笑的青春期嗓音说出来
Uh, sorry, it's just hard to focus on what you're saying
我没法集中注意力听你说的内容
with that squeaky puberty voice you got there.
我的啥
My what?
没啥好害臊的  迪普
It's nothing to be ashamed of, Dipper.
你的声音很搞笑
Your voice is hilarious.
你是说我的声音沙哑吗
Are you saying my voice cracks?
我声音不沙哑
My voice doesn't crack.
哥们儿  毫无冒犯之意  不过你的声音确实经常沙哑
Dude, no offense, but it cracks so much
我们还用你声音合成了一段电子音乐
we've already made a techno remix out of it.
见到你很高兴
Nice to meet you.
我叫迪普·派恩斯
My name's Dipper Pines.
派  派  派  派恩斯  派恩斯
P-p-pines, Pines, Pines.
见到你很高兴
Nice to meet you.
派  派  派  派恩斯  派恩斯
P-p-pines, Pines, Pines.
我的声音真像这样么
Do I really sound like that?
噢  我最喜欢的那部分来了
Oh! Here comes my favorite part!
快停下  伙计们
Stop it, guys!
给我
Gimme that!
小猪转圈
Spin the pig!
连我的叹气声都那么奇怪
Ugh! Even my sighs sound weird.
-你好啊  -啊
- Hello there!  - Aah!
我无意中听到了你的烦心事
I couldn't help but overhear yer sitchy-ation!
我是老头子麦戈科特
Old man McGucket!
兼职发明家
Part-time inventor!
你为什么要往自己手上吐口水呢
Why did you spit on your hand?
我没想过哎
I don't rightly know!
嘿  我记得你
Hey, I remember you!
你的机器人差点害死我
Your robot almost killed me!
过来  跟我到那黑暗危险的小巷里
Come here! Follow me into this dark, dangerous alley!
最近我在研究一种可以改变声音的药水
Lately I been a-tinkerizin' with a voice altering tonic,
为了改变我那听上去很吓人的声音
on account of my horrifyin' voice!
你可以跑  但我仍然能追到你的噩梦里
You can run, but I'll still be in yer nightmares!
这个真的能改变我的声音么
This will really fix my voice?
谢了
Thanks! Ah!
明天早晨  你的声音将焕然一新
Come mornin', you'll sound like a new man!
前提是你能活下来
If you survive.
早上好  迪普
Good morning, Dipper.
我成功了  我成功了
I did it! I did it!
我的声音变了
Now I have a new voice!
早上好  梅宝  谁是我最喜欢的梅宝呢
'morning, Mabel. Who's my favorite Mabel?
你是谁
Who are you?
你对我弟弟做了什么
What have you done with my brother?
（注：据制片人，梅宝比迪普早出生五分钟）
迪普
Dipper!
我要把你从这个附在你身体里的巫师手中救出来
I'll save you from this body-switching warlock!
梅宝  是我啊
Mabel, it's me!
这是我的新嗓音
This is my voice now.
听上去很酷吧
I sound awesome.
酷毙了
Sound awesome.
我知道男生会变声  但这个声也太奇怪了
I knew boys' voices changed, but this is weird.
又糟又怪
Weird and bad.
梅宝  这是迄今为止我遇到的最棒的事了
Mabel, this is the best thing that ever happened to me.
来打个恶作剧电话吧
And just think of the prank calls.
你好
Hello?
你好  我是美利坚合众国总统
Hello. This is the president of the United States of America.
我打电话是要和你说
I'm calling to tell you...
什么  你是谁
What? Who is this?
哈哈哈  厉害吧
Ho-ho-ho! Magnificent!
梅宝不喜欢
Mabel no like.
你好吗  苏斯
How you diddly doing, Soos?
-杀了他  -噢
- Kill it!  - Oh!
用火烧死他  大家快跑
Kill it with fire! Everyone flee!
有没有搞错啊兄弟
What gives, man?
你们都取笑我原来的声音
You guys all made fun of my old voice.
我还以为你们会喜欢这个新的呢
I thought you'd like the new one.
老兄  至少你的声音得像个真人吧
Dude, at least before you sounded like a real person.
你现在的声音就像个给广告配音的怪人
Now you sound like some kind of weird commercial dude.
我去找斯坦
I'll find Stan.
他会喜欢我的新声音的  走着瞧吧
He'll like my new voice. You'll see!
休息一下广告之后精彩继续
I'll be right back after these messages.
我的意思是  再见
I, uh, I mean, goodbye.
斯坦叔公  斯坦叔公  你在哪儿呢  斯坦叔公
Grunkle Stan. Grunkle Stan! Where are you, Grunkle Stan?
嘿  我记得你的声音
Huh? I'd know that voice anywhere!
你就是给我打恶作剧电话的那个人
You're the guy who prank called me earlier!
不不  我不是
No. No, I'm not.
我只是个十二岁的小男孩
I'm just a 12-year-old boy!
你以为我会信吗  你个发着怪声的小子
You expect me to believe that, you crazy-voiced punk?
等等  不  哎呀
W-wait! No! Aiyee!
有个专打恶作剧电话的人跑掉了  咱们快去抓
There's a prank caller on the loose! Let's get him!
好的  走  去抓他
Yeah! Come on! Come on, let's get him!
我逃
Escape!
麦戈科特  你的发明就是个灾难
McGucket! Your invention was a catastrophe!
这可能也是我住在垃圾堆的原因
That's probably why I live in the dump!
我的亲姐姐都不认识我了
My own sister didn't recognize me.
大家都被我吓得乱跑
I scared away crowds!
连我的哭声都很可笑
I even sound ridiculous when I cry.
啊  我知道你的问题了
Well, now, here's yer problem!
我给你拿错药了
I gave you the wrong drinky-majig!
这个是给旁白播音员用的
This one's for voiceover professional.
我敢肯定我这儿还有更好的声音
Ah! I'm sure I've got a better voice in here somewhere.
那就好  快点找
Good! Hurry up.
你来得很及时
You got here just in time.
不然一到日落  你就
Come sundown, you'd have
又会变回原来那可笑的声音了
reverted back to your ridiculous old voice.
是很可笑  对吧
It was ridiculous, wasn't it?
迪  迪  迪  迪  迪普·派恩斯
D-d-d-d-dipper Pines,
这就是我
That's me!
谨以此献给我的弟弟
This remix is dedicated to my brother.
迪普  你的声音是独一无二的
Dipper, your voice is one of a kind.
哥们儿  我从来没听过像这样的东西
Dude, I never heard anything like it.
音乐结束
R-r-remix over!
准备好换一个新声音了吗
You ready for yer new voice?
这个会永久有效的哦
This one should be permanent!
嘿  伙计们
Hey, guys.
-迪普  -哥们儿  你终于又回来了
- Dipper! - Oh, dude, you're back!
是啊  我想我是明白了
Yeah. I guess I realized
即使我的声音不是最完美的
that even though my voice might not be perfect,
不过那也是我的  我不会再因为任何事去改变它了
It's still mine, and I wouldn't change it for anything,
不管这个试管里装的是啥
Not even for whatever was in this new vial.
那你把其余的药水弄哪去了
So what did you do with the rest of that potion?
我给倒进斯坦的咖啡里了
I dumped it in Stan's coffee.
你们谁看见我的腰带了么
Any of you kids seen my girdle?
我的腰带哪儿去了
Where my girdle at?
怎么了  有什么好笑的  我是斯坦叔公
What? What's so funny? I'm Grunkle Stan!
小屁孩竟然在嘲笑他们的叔公
Kids laughin'. Laughin' at their grunkle.
我用我的小眼睛瞄了下  发现有东西是黑色的
I spy, with my little eye, something that is Black!
我知道  是所有一切
Ooh! Ooh! Everything.
为苏斯鼓掌
Yay for Soos!
伙计们  咱们来转圈圈打发时间吧
Hey, guys, who wants to pass the time by spinning?
大家一起转
Everyone spin!
不要
No.
迪普的痛苦挺有喜感  不过我觉得有点看腻了
Dipper's pain is funny, but I'm starting to get bored.
苏斯  你讲个故事
Soos, tell a story.
哦  好吧
Really? Okay.
故事的名字叫  苏斯超棒的弹球故事
This story is called "Soos's really great pinball story."
这个名字还行么  是不是还得有双关语什么的
Is that a good title? Do they have to be, like, puns or whatever?
苏斯
超棒的
弹球故事
这个名字还行么？
是不是还得有双关语什么的？
加油  加油  加油
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
就是这样了  伙计们  经过整整四年的努力
This is it, dudes. After four long years of trying,
我终于有可能在斯坦诡异的
I might finally get the high score
老式弹球机上赢得高分了
on Stan's creepy old pinball machine.
如果我能做到
If I do this, I'll go down
我将会被载入弹球史册  像萨尔  加夫一样
in pinball history with the likes of Sal, Gaff,
当然  还有便便
and of course Poo.
你有没有试过倾斜一下机器
Have you ever tried maybe just tilting the machine?
我不知道哎
I don't know, dudes.
那样是不是犯规了呢  就像  违反规则
Isn't breaking the rules, like, against the rules?
去他的犯规  晃机子  晃机子
Nuts to the rules! Tilt! Tilt! Tilt!
失败  你个蠢货
Failure. You stink!
够了  好吧  你们准备好了吗
All right, that's it. Ready, kids?
晃  晃  晃  晃
Tilt! Tilt! Tilt! Tilt!
别晃  朋友  别晃啊
Quit tiltin', pardner. Quit tiltin', pardner.
晃机子
Tilt!
正中红心
Bull's eye!
新的高分记录产生了
New high score!
-好耶  -好耶
- Oh, yes! - All right!
这是我人生中最幸福的时刻
This is the best moment of my life.
完胜我上一个最幸福时刻
This totally beats my old best moment.
这是不对的  你们作弊
That ain't right. You cheated.
那又怎么样  你能咋地
Oh, yeah? What are you gonna do about it?
你只是台弹球机而已  弹球机
You're just a pinball game, pinball game.
气死你  气死你
Taunt, taunt.
伙计们  有一道
Uh, guys? There's an awful
好强的绿光从游戏里发出来了
lot of green lightning coming out of that game.
只是寻常的绿光罢了
No, that's the normal amount of green lightning.
再睡五分钟不行么
Ugh. Five more minutes.
啊  那不是普通的闹铃声
Aah! That's not a normal alarm clock.
苏斯  我们进游戏里了
Soos! We're inside the game!
-太疯狂了  -我的神呐
- Crazy. - Sweet moses!
无声的惊叹
Hushed exclamation of wonder.
真帅
Awesome!
砰  砰  砰
Boing! Boing! Boing!
哥们  如果这只是一个梦  我希望永远都不要醒来
Dude, if this is a dream, I never wanna wake up!
这事好办
That can be arranged.
朋友们  欢迎来到风滚草恐怖世界
Welcome to tumbleweed terror, pardners!
你不就是那个骷髅牛仔吗
Hey, it's the skeleton cowboy guy.
你把我吸进你的游戏  是为了庆祝我
Did you zap me into your game to congratulate me
登上高分榜么  哥们儿  我打败便便啦
On getting the high score? I beat poo, dude.
如果我记得没错  我提醒过你们不要作弊
Hardly. If'n I do recall, I warned y'all not to cheat.
我努力表现得像绅士一样
I tried to be gentleman-like,
但是我受够被摇晃了
but I'm plum sick of being tilted.
所以我要反抗了  我要来摇晃你们
So now I reckon. I'm gonna tilt you.
是吗  那好  接招吧
Oh, yeah? Well-- well, take this!
嗷  再接招  好疼
Ow! And this! Ow! It hurts!
我真希望这有用  哦天啊
I wish this was working better! Oh, dude!
苏斯
Soos!
你们做好准备挑战
Get yourselves ready for the...
多球模式
Multi-ball!
快去那儿
Over there!
你们在哪儿
Where are you?
不为作弊而好好教训你们一顿我是不会罢休的
I'm not done teachin' you a lesson about cheating yet!
我们怎样才能离开这里  快想想办法吧  大伙儿
How are we ever gonna get out of here? Think, guys!
我在想  但这有些困难
I'm trying, but it's hard
这位美丽的弹球少妇正在分散我的注意力
with that gorgeous pinball wench distracting me.
好吧  别担心了  各位
Okay, don't worry, guys.
我知道这台机器的每个细节
I know every inch of this machine.
这里面有个手动的电源开关
There's a manual power switch inside.
我可以偷偷跑进去把游戏关掉
I can sneak in there and turn off the game,
但我们必须分散那个牛仔的注意力
but we'll have to distract the cowboy guy.
你们两个中有谁擅长上窜下跳的
Are either of you good at jumping up and down
再弄些恼人的噪音
and making annoying noises?
我出场的时候到了
My time has come.
行了  我们快走吧  苏斯  苏斯
All right, let's go, Soos. Soos?
我说  你是想待会儿和我一起
So are you, like, doing anything later or--
好吧
Right.
快出来  别躲着  淘气鬼们
Come on out and show yourselves, varmints!
听着  好好看看我要干什么
Listen to me and look at what I'm doing!
有些不对劲啊
Somethin' ain't right here.
看这里  看这里
Distraction! Distraction!
我倒要看看会发生什么
Let me see where this is goin'.
（电源）
什么  你们去哪儿了
Yippe-ti-yi-- what? Where are ya?
真该死  真希望我有个脖子
Durn it, I wish I had a neck!
苏斯  喂  你怎么样了
Soos! Psst! What's going on?
只要按下那个开关就好了
Just press the switch already!
好吧  我是想要那么做  但是我在想
Okay, so I was gonna do that, but I've been thinking.
根据这个看来
According to this,
关掉电源就会把最高分永远地消除了
turning off the power erases the high score permanently.
（警告：关闭电源将消除所有数据）
那个分数就像  我人生中最大的成就一样
That score is, like, my one big life accomplishment.
什么  要是你不快点我们就要死在这里了
What? If you don't hurry up we could die in here!
话是这么说没错  但是  生命的意义何在
Fair point. But, what is life anyway,
与永恒的最高分相比孰轻孰重呢
When compared to the immortality of a high score?
苏斯  你疯了吗
Soos! Are you out of your--
你们在那儿呢
There y'all are.
准备好见见你们的造物主吧  孩子们
Get ready to meet yer maker, kids!
我的造物主是球威游戏  位于华盛顿州雷德蒙德
My maker is ballway games in Redmond, Washington.
梅宝
Mabel!
-苏斯  -苏斯  求你了
- SOOS!  - SOOS, PLEASE!
关掉它
Turn it off!
再见了  我的最高分
Goodbye, high score!
你们还好吗
Oh, you dudes okay?
嗯  苏斯  你做到了  你拯救了我们
Yeah, Soos. You did it! You freed us!
嘿  兄弟  我很抱歉你失去了最高分
Hey, man, I'm sorry you had to lose your high score.
没关系啦  我现在获得了新的人生成就了
That's okay. I got a new life accomplishment now:
就是救了你们的命
saving you dudes.
你们觉得那位弹球少妇会给我打电话么
You think that pinball wench will call me?
这也太扯了
I can't believe this nonsense!
魔法药剂  苏斯赢了什么东西
Magic tonics? Soos winning at something?
你们从哪里想出来这种玩意的
what do you come up these stuff?
我来给你们讲个好故事
I'll tell you a good story.
这个故事叫做“斯坦叔公赢了橄榄球碗”
It's called "Grunkle Stan wins the football bowl."
派恩斯先生
Mr. Pines.
我本以为年纪大的人都没用了
I thought old folks were useless,
但你却给我和我沾沾自喜的朋友们上了一课
But you taught me and my gloating friends a lesson.
这是你的橄榄球优胜奖杯  派恩斯先生
Here's your football winning trophy, Mr. Pines!
谢谢  美丽的姑娘  单凭我自己是不可能赢得这个奖杯的
Thanks, beautiful woman, but I couldn't have done it
多亏我的好助手  橄榄机器人
without my sidekick, foot-bot.
谢谢你创造了我  爸爸
Thank you for building me, daddy.
我爱你  斯坦
I love you, Stan.
拜托
Come on.
什么  那故事不是很精彩吗
What? That story was great.
为了让小孩子爱听  我甚至编出个会说话的机器人呢
I even threw in a talking robot for the kids.
好吧  好吧  我要来讲一个一点都不差劲的故事
Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna tell a non-terrible story,
故事的名字是
A story called...
说真话的烦恼
Thoothache.
这个吸引眼球的家伙将会让我好好赚一笔
This attraction is gonna make me a fortune!
好好待那头熊  灯芯绒
Easy with that bear, corduroy!
我要他像展览品一样闪耀
I need him in showroom condition!
不  不
No! No!
他们在拥抱呢
Aw! They're hugging!
让我理理清楚
So let me get this straight.
你的计划是教会这头熊骑自行车
Your plan is to teach this bear to ride a bicycle?
不  拜托  大家都见过会骑自行车的熊
Nah, come on. Everyone's seen a bicycle-riding bear.
不  不是  我是要教这头熊
No, no. I'm gonna teach this bear...
开车
To drive!
黄灯表示要加速了
And the yellow light means speed up.
糟糕
Uh-oh.
请问你们有什么问题吗  警官
What seems to be the problem, officers?
你现在最好有个足够好的理由给我解释这个
Now there had better be a darn good explanation for this.
哦  有啊
Oh, there is.
你看  我是个老年人  也没有多少时日了
You see, I'm a very old man, not long for this earth,
医生就给我配了一头导盲熊
and the doctor's assigned me a seeing-eye bear
以防遇到紧急情况  他好开车送我去医院
To drive me to the hospital in case of emergencies.
这是真的吗  那你的医嘱在哪里
Is that right? Then where's your doctor's note?
当然  就在这儿  在我的外套里
Why, it's right here, inside my jacket!
啊  找到了
Ah! There you go!
（斯坦生病了  需要一头熊  -麦迪森医生）
好吧  麦迪森医生的医嘱毋庸置疑
Well, I can't argue with dr. Medicine.
去医院吧  小亲亲
To the hospital, honeypants!
斯坦叔公  你怎么可以对警察说谎呢
Grunkle Stan, how could you lie to those policemen?
难道你不知道撒谎总是不对的吗
Don't you know lying is always wrong?
梅宝  等你到了我这个年纪
Mabel, when you get to be my age,
你就会明白了  有时候
You'll learn that sometimes
你不得不为了更大的利益而扭曲事实
You have to bend the truth for the greater good.
嘿  你们有没有人见到我那盘意大利面
Hey, has anyone seen my plate of spaghetti?
没有
No.
但我肯定苏斯见过  你知道他就是个吃货
But I bet Soos has. You know how he likes to eat.
今天真是灰暗的一天  谢了  斯坦叔公
This is a dark day. Thanks, Grunkle Stan!
看见了吗  更大的利益
See? Greater good.
摇摇  对斯坦叔公我究竟该怎么做
Waddles, what am I gonna do about Grunkle Stan?
他不能再这样说谎下去了
He needs to stop lying.
我明白  但我们要怎么阻止他呢
I know! But how do we stop him?
也许你应该看看迪普的日记
Maybe you should check Dipper's journal.
哼哼
Oink, oink!
再说一次“哼哼”
Say "Oink" One more time.
哼哼
Oink, oink.
摇摇  你真是个天才
Waddles, you genius!
“真心话假牙埋藏在森林深处的一个树桩下
"Buried 'neath a tree stump in the deep forest are truth teeth,
佩戴它的人会被迫失去说谎的能力” 嗯
which force upon the wearer an inability to lie." Hmm.
什么情况  怎么了  梅宝
Aah! What's going on? What? Mabel?
快问快答
Quick question.
迪普的意大利面去哪儿了
What happened to Dipper's spaghetti plate?
被我吃了  因为我很少甚至从来
I ate it, because I have little to no concern
不在乎他人的物品  或考虑他们的感受
for other people's possessions or emotions.
呃  好奇怪的坦白
Huh. That was strangely candid.
就好像我说不了谎似的  好吧  晚安
Almost as if I'm unable to lie. Well, goodnight!
你什么  这主意听起来真可怕
You what? That seems like a horrible idea!
多棒啊
It's great!
现在他必须说真话了
Now he has to tell the truth.
这是炒肉  给你们
Scrambled meat, here it is.
斯坦叔公  你每天午休的时候都在秘密地做些什么啊
Stan, what do you do in secret every day during your lunch break?
通常我都在这一小时里狠狠地给自己挠痒痒
Usually I spend the hour aggressively scratching myself
挠的地方我就不说了
in places I shouldn't mention.
现在我要避免眼神交流了
Now I'm going to avoid making eye contact
方式是假装我在看这份报纸
by pretending to read this newspaper,
然后再去卫生间并且不洗手
And go to the bathroom without washing my hands.
呃  有点烦人啊
Well, that was disturbing.
别担心  迪普
Don't worry, Dipper.
说真话总是好的
The truth is always a good thing.
嘿  打扰了
Hey, excuse me.
你觉得这件T恤的尺寸适合我吗
Do you think this t-shirt is my size?
别管这件T恤了  嘿  大伙们
Never mind the t-shirt! Hey, everybody!
快看看这家伙又怪异又难看的脸呀
Look at this guy's abnormal and unattractive face!
对不起  真抱歉
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
我在计算我的税务
Doing my taxes.
我逃税骗税
斯坦叔公  你为什么要写这些啊
Uh, Grunkle Stan, why did you write this?
因为我会定期涉嫌大量的税务欺诈
Because I regularly commit massive tax fraud.
这东西还是放那儿比较好
Might wanna tuck that one away there.
哦  不
Oh, no!
有时我在想  人生不就是这样吗
Sometimes I think, is this all there is?
生活是不是只是一个可怕的  没有笑点的笑话
Is life just some kind of horrific joke without a punch line?
那我们都不过是在耗费时间罢了
That we're all just biding our time
直到美好的  安详的死亡来解放我们
until the sweet, sweet release of death?
孩子们
Kids!
我觉得我背上长了个东西
I think I have a growth forming on my back!
只是不想跟你们隐瞒什么
Just wanted to be honest with you guys!
我再也受不了了  梅宝
I can't take it anymore, Mabel!
你必须把那副假牙从他嘴里拿出来
You have to take those teeth out of his mouth.
但是那样的话他又要和从前一样说谎了
But then he'd be a liar again!
还能有比现在这样更糟的情况了吗
Could is possibly be any worse than this?
经过我们的进一步调查发现
So after further investigation,
重力泉根本没有什么麦迪森医生
Turns out there is no Dr. Medicine in Gravity Falls.
你最好能有个足够好的理由来解释解释
You'd better have a durn good explanation for this.
我是有理由的
Oh, and I do!
你瞧  是我骗了你们
You see, I lied to you.
而且  我还在残疾人的车位停车
In addition, I've been parking in handicapped spaces,
入店行窃烟花爆竹
shoplifting fireworks,
还有跨越多条州界来走私濒危动物
And smuggling endangered animals across multiple state lines.
还有  你真胖
Also, you're fat.
这都是真的吗
Is all this true?
不  不是  不是真的  对吗  梅宝
No, no, it's not true... right, Mabel?
呃  警官们
Uh... sirs,
我得毫无保留地对你们实话实说
I have to be completely and totally honest with you.
我们的斯坦叔公是
Our great uncle Stan is...
是  呃
Is... ugh!
斯坦是
Stan is...
私下里是一个罪案小说作家
secretly a crime fiction writer!
什么
What?
是啊  他刚刚告诉你的就是
Yeah! He was just telling you
他即将要写的精彩情节中一个人物的故事
about a character from his upcoming page-turner
罪犯老爷爷
crime grandpa.
他的一生中从来不犯罪的
He's never committed a crime in his life!
还有  你是不是瘦了
Also, have you lost weight?
可算是有人发现了
Finally, someone noticed.
哇  一个作家
Wow, an author!
你能教我读书么
Can you teach me how to read?
什么  作家
What? Author?
作家  都是小说大师啊
Writer-- masters of fiction!
晚安  警官们
Good night, officers!
嘿  你还好吗
Hey, you all right?
真不敢相信我竟然说谎了
I can't believe I lied!
梅宝  这是为了更大的利益
Mabel, it was for the greater good.
是啊  更大的利益
Yeah. The greater good.
喂  警察局吗
Hello, police station?
是  我忘记告诉他们其实我还逃税骗税呢
Yeah, I forgot to tell 'em about my tax fraud.
不是  是税务欺诈
No, tax fraud.
快拿出来
Get 'em out!
孩子们你们怎么了
What's gotten into you kids?
我们得找个地方处理掉这东西
We have to find a place to get rid of these!
然后我就再也没见过那个装着魔力假牙的箱子了
And I never saw that box full of magical teeth again.
等等  就在那儿呢
Oh, wait, there it is.
好耶  我的鞋子
Oh, sweet, my shoes.
我喜欢那头熊的部分
I liked the part with the bear.
其他的听起来都乱七八糟的
The rest seemed pretty farfetched.
梅宝  我们都已经知道那个故事了
Mabel, we already know that story.
我们刚刚经历过
We just lived through it.
那么  如果我们现在正在经历那个故事
So, if we're living through that story right now,
究竟会是什么结局
How does it end?
大伙们  你们看见了吗
Guys, do you see that?
-那是什么  -哦  不
- Oh, what is that?  - Oh, no!
-我们要去哪里  -我的天哪
- Where are we going?  - Oh, my god!
我们  我们在哪里
Where... where are we?
看  是小屋
Look! The shack!
这意味着
Which means...
我们又从洞口出来了
We came right back out the top
而且似乎时间也没有流逝
And I don't think any time has passed.
这一定是什么虫洞之类的东西
It must be some kind of wormhole
是啊  老弟  那听来可科学了呢  肯定没错
Yeah, dude, that sounds science enough to be true.
但  这也太不可思议了吧
But, but that's impossible.
没有人会相信我们的
No one will believe us.
也许这个故事只要我们自己知道就行了
Maybe this is one story we should keep to ourselves.
同意
Agree.
没事的啦
He'll be fine.
这也太蠢了
This is stupid.